일반적으로 embeddings을 배울 수 있는
Word2Vec에 대한 2개의 상세한 기술과 방법이 있습니다.
Two more technical details
about Word 2 Vec and
about methods to learn
embeddings in general.
첫번째로, embeddings을 학습하는 방법 때문에
First, because of the way embeddings are
trained, it's often better to measure
인접함을 계산하기 위해서 L2 대신에
cosine distance을 자주 사용합니다.
the closeness using a cosine
distance instead of L2, for example.
cosine  distance을 사용하는 이유는
That's because the length
of the embedding vector
embedding vector의 길이는 분류와는
상관이 없기 때문입니다.
is not relevant to the classification.
실제로, 모든 embedding vectors을
정규하는데 자주 사용됩니다.
In fact, it's often better to
normalize all embedding vectors
단일한 형태로 단순화 하기 위해서..
to simply have unit norm.
두번째는, 많은 단어들을 예측하는
문제를 가지고 있습니다.
Second, we have the issue of
trying to predict words, and
there are lots of them.
우리가 구성한 Word2Vec에서는
작은 vector로 embed할 단어를 가지고 있으며,
So in Word 2 Vec we have this set up,
we have a word that we're going to embed
weight와 biases을 갖는 단순한
선형 모델로 적합할 수 있고,
into a small vector, then feed that into
a simple linear model with weights and
softmax probability로 결과가 출력됩니다.
biases and
that outputs a softmax probability.
이것은 입력된 단어의 상황에서 다른 단어의
상황을 비교하는 것입니다.
This is then compared to the target
which is another word in the context
of the input word.
이 과정의 문제는 사전안에는
많은 단어가 있다는 것입니다.
The problem of course is
that there might be many,
many words in our vocabulary.
그리고, 모든 단어의 softmax함수를
계산하는 것은 매우 비효율적일 수 있습니다.
And computing the softmax function of
all those words can be very inefficient.
그러나, 당신은 트릭을 사용할 수 있습니다.
But you can use a trick.
softmax을 다루는 대신에
라벨이 1의 확률을 갖는다면,
Instead of treating the softmax as
if the label had probability of 1,
모든 다른 단어는 0의 확률을 갖게됩니다.
and every other word
had probability of 0,
당신은 대상이 아닌 단어를
샘플을 뽑을 수 있습니다.
you can sample the words
that are not the targets,
다른 단어가 없는것 같이
단어중 조금만 뽑습니다.
pick only a handful of them and act
as if the other words were not there.
각각의 예제에 대해서 negative
targets을 샘플링하는 아이디어는
This idea of sampling
the negative targets for
자주 sampled softmax라고 언급됩니다.
each example is often
called sampled softmax.
그리고, 성능에 부담이 없이
빠르게 수행됩니다.
And it makes things faster
at no cost in performance.
이것이 모든 작업입니다.
That's all there is to it.
당신은 텍스트의 거대한 말뭉치를 가지고 오고,
각각의 단어를 찾고, 단어를 embed합니다.
You take your large corpus of texts,
look at each word, embed it, and
그리고 이웃한 단어를 예측합니다.
predict its neighbors.
당신이 수행한 것들은 단어로부터
vector로 맵핑한 것이고,
What you get out of that is
a mapping from words to vectors
유사한 단어는 서로 근접하도록
가지고 위치시키는 것입니다.
where similar words are going to
be close to each other.